<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Japan Trip 2010 on Scott R Christian</title>
    <link>/categories/japan-trip-2010/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Japan Trip 2010 on Scott R Christian</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 06:20:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/japan-trip-2010/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Osaka!</title>
      <link>/2010/07/15/osaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 06:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/07/15/osaka/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) Osaka Castle, Osaka Aquarium, Kobe&#xA;** Photoswipe Album **&#xA;I visited Osaka for a few days and stayed at my stepmom&amp;rsquo;s friend, Naomi&amp;rsquo;s house. They have two kids, Kizuna, 4, and So, 2 years old.&#xA;They are really good kids, although really noisy! It had been 3 years since I saw Naomi last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imperial Palace Gardens and Roppongi</title>
      <link>/2010/07/15/imperial-palace-gardens-and-roppongi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 01:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/07/15/imperial-palace-gardens-and-roppongi/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) Imperial Palace Garden and Roppongi&#xA;Not really much to say about this trip. Went to Tokyo, saw the imperial gardens (which are huge) and took the subway to Aoyama, walked to Roppongi.&#xA;** Photoswipe album **&#xA;Imperial Palace gardens. There were a lot of people just bumming around napping under the trees and such.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiroshima</title>
      <link>/2010/07/15/hiroshima/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 01:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/07/15/hiroshima/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) Sorry it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I last updated. I used the JR pass to go afield and didn&amp;rsquo;t have room to carry my laptop and fit enough clothes to last.&#xA;Hiroshima Photo Set ** Enter Hiroshima photo swipe album here **&#xA;On my trip to Hiroshima.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mt. Fuji</title>
      <link>/2010/07/05/mt-fuji/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 09:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/07/05/mt-fuji/</guid>
      <description>From Shinjuku to Kawaguchiko to the Top (The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) So when I was planning for my trip to see the area around Mt. Fuji, I never really thought i&amp;rsquo;d end up climbing it.&#xA;Mr. Takata helped me to plan the fastest route of trains to Kawaguchiko, which leads up to the 5th station of Mt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo and Local Area…</title>
      <link>/2010/06/29/tokyo-and-local-area/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 06:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/06/29/tokyo-and-local-area/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) The past few days I have been exploring Chiba and the Tokyo area, which is huge. I&amp;rsquo;ve been to Akihabara, Ueno Park, Tokyo National Museum, Tokyo Station, Wadakura fountain park, Shinjuku, Chiba-Minato, and Chiba Castle. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken a lot of pictures,but I will try to organize them the best I can and see what I can do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Takatas</title>
      <link>/2010/06/25/the-takatas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 15:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/06/25/the-takatas/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) Honestly, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I could have found better hosts to stay with in Japan than the Takatas! They are very nice and helpful to me. I love having discussions with Mr. Takata. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot from him so far; he is a very smart and interesting person to talk to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiba City</title>
      <link>/2010/06/24/chiba-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 12:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/06/24/chiba-city/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) Here are a few pictures of where I am staying in Chiba City.&#xA;Here is my room. It&amp;rsquo;s small but really nice. You can&amp;rsquo;t see it, but across the room from the dresser is a closet where the futon I sleep on at night is stored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First day – Chiba City Zoo</title>
      <link>/2010/06/21/first-day-chiba-city-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 06:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/06/21/first-day-chiba-city-zoo/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) I went to bed around 9:00 pm last night, and got up around 6! No jet lag so far really.&#xA;Today I decided I would go to Chiba City Zoo. It&amp;rsquo;s close by. Only had to take a monorail for about 15 minutes. Mr. Takata explained to me how to use the transportation system and lent me a Pasmo card, which is a card you can load up with money in order to avoid buying tickets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finally here</title>
      <link>/2010/06/20/finally-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 03:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/06/20/finally-here/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) I&amp;rsquo;m in Japan! The flight was smooth, and when I arrived at Narita Airport I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any trouble getting through customs.&#xA;I met up with Mr. Takata, and from there we drove to his house in Chiba City, which was about a 40 minute drive. The Takata&amp;rsquo;s are really nice!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOING TO JAPAN!… soon.</title>
      <link>/2010/06/19/going-to-japan-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 12:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/06/19/going-to-japan-soon/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) Hey everyone. I figured I would make a introduction blog post for you all for some background informations.&#xA;So I&amp;rsquo;m Scott. 18 years of age.&#xA;I just finished my first year of college! Definitely wasn&amp;rsquo;t the crazy party all the time college that most everyone I knew was looking forward too, but I got some good grades in and that&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s going to count in the long run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Post!</title>
      <link>/2010/06/18/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 16:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010/06/18/first-post/</guid>
      <description>(The following post is from 2010. I imported my blog posts from my month long trip to Japan for posterity and to remember fondly!) Hey guys.&#xA;This is my first blog, and i&amp;rsquo;m not entirely sure how to use all the features, but i can post! Thats the main thing.&#xA;The name of the blog comes from my name in katakana directly translated to english.&#xA;スコット -&amp;gt; Su ko tto</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
